<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>Psychedelic Panorama of Foo</title>
 <link href="http://r351574nc3.github.io/" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://r351574nc3.github.io"/>
 <updated>2013-10-04T11:37:10-07:00</updated>
 <id>http://r351574nc3.github.io</id>
 <author>
   <name>r351574nc3</name>
   <email>r351574nc3@gmail.com</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Gangplank Open Hacknight: Return of Sugru Build Night</title>
   <link href="http://r351574nc3.github.io/gangplank/2013/10/04/gangplank-open-hacknight-return-of-sugru-build-night"/>
   <updated>2013-10-04T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://r351574nc3.github.io/gangplank/2013/10/04/gangplank-open-hacknight-return-of-sugru-build-night</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img alt='Sugru packets piled up' src='https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-SGH1_JbmteM/UexTKg-DZBI/AAAAAAAAJmU/taRWkwkxCSc/w780-h583-no/13+-+1' title='Sugru packets piled up' width='480' /&gt;
&lt;h2 id='sugru_build_night_returns'&gt;Sugru Build Night Returns!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those of you who remember the &lt;a href='/gangplank/2013/07/30/gangplank-open-hacknight-sugru-build-night/'&gt;Original Sugru Build Night&lt;/a&gt; from earlier in July, it&amp;#8217;s back by popular demand! What&amp;#8217;s changed? Checkout my intro video below.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;embed id='movie_player' height='385' type='application/x-shockwave-flash' src='http://www.youtube.com/v/4lxGdnWn2Ic?hd=1&amp;showinfo=0&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;et=OEgsToPDskJni4UfFH3f0WbK6L_15ohf&amp;amp;hl=en_US&amp;amp;fs=1' allowfullscreen='false' name='movie_player' style='' width='640' quality='high' /&gt;
&lt;h2 id='more_sugru'&gt;More Sugru!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the original Sugru Build Night, we knew we wanted to do more. We wanted to go higher, shine brighter, and just be awesomer than ever before. We just didn&amp;#8217;t know how. We were consistently blocked by the semantically nullifying, &amp;#8220;we don&amp;#8217;t know what we don&amp;#8217;t know.&amp;#8221; Then, the idea struck us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This time, we want to do a class. Just come to learn about it. We&amp;#8217;ll do a run down on various usages and proposals for new or existing projects. The hope is that one of us will come up with something new and exciting or at the very least expand their hacking knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id='you_can_still_bring_a_project'&gt;You Can Still Bring a Project!&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you already have a project, that&amp;#8217;s great! Your project exists because you had a need and you willed it into creation. That&amp;#8217;s just the kind of person you are. You discover problems and you fix them. Sugru will earn its way into your toolbelt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just as before. If you bring your project in you can:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn from people have designed projects and used Sugru.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Get people to become involved in your project to help you.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Discover new uses for Sugru.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;See how Sugru can be fitted for your project.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Dream of new projects that use Sugru.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Become a Sugru project building machine.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Gangplank Open Hacknight: Sugru Build Night</title>
   <link href="http://r351574nc3.github.io/gangplank/2013/07/30/gangplank-open-hacknight-sugru-build-night"/>
   <updated>2013-07-30T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://r351574nc3.github.io/gangplank/2013/07/30/gangplank-open-hacknight-sugru-build-night</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;img alt='Sugru packets piled up' src='https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-SGH1_JbmteM/UexTKg-DZBI/AAAAAAAAJmU/taRWkwkxCSc/w780-h583-no/13+-+1' title='Sugru packets piled up' width='480' /&gt;
&lt;h2 id='the_discovery_of_sugru'&gt;The Discovery of Sugru&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just recently I discovered this awesome product that helped me make things and think about making stuff in new and interesting ways. It&amp;#8217;s this stuff that feels like putty, but it&amp;#8217;s so much more. It&amp;#8217;s a self-setting, moldable rubber called Sugru. Right away, I have a number of uses for fixing things. It&amp;#8217;s waterproof, heat tolerant, and adheres to just about anything. Even if you don&amp;#8217;t make stuff, it&amp;#8217;s immediately useful to the world for fixing. The great thing is that it&amp;#8217;s not even really a challenge for making either. It&amp;#8217;s your own moldable rubber. That&amp;#8217;s awesome, right!? How many projects can you think of that you have where you would improve it if you had your own moldable rubber? Or how many projects have you not been able to get off the ground because you couldn&amp;#8217;t fabricate your own rubber?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id='gangplank_hacknight_sponsored_by_sugru'&gt;Gangplank Hacknight Sponsored by Sugru&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, that was me. I was that guy that had projects I couldn&amp;#8217;t complete because I didn&amp;#8217;t know I needed Sugru. The great thing is that the guys at Sugru recognize this. They sent Gangplank Tucson a good amount of Sugru to help us get you started or maybe even re-started on your project. They are sponsoring a Sugru exclusive hacknight at Gangplank Tucson.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The purpose of Gangplank Hacknights is to establish a critical mass of power, intelligence, tools, resources, and ambition for your project to snowball into its destiny. Bring your project and interact, network, or get the help to make your project a success. It doesn&amp;#8217;t matter if your project is a learning project or a hobby project. Bring it. Success isn&amp;#8217;t dictated by the significance of your project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you bring your project in you can:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learn from people have designed projects and used Sugru.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Get people to become involved in your project to help you.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Discover new uses for Sugru.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;See how Sugru can be fitted for your project.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Dream of new projects that use Sugru.&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;Become a Sugru project building machine.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>How To Use Watir and RSpec to Generate Tsung Tests</title>
   <link href="http://r351574nc3.github.io/development/2013/03/14/how-to-use-watir-and-rspec-to-generate-tsung-tests"/>
   <updated>2013-03-14T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://r351574nc3.github.io/development/2013/03/14/how-to-use-watir-and-rspec-to-generate-tsung-tests</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id='overview'&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Developing and managing tsung tests performance tests can be difficult because of the immense amount over verbose XML. Thankfully, much of what you test for performance is already available as an automated user interface test via Watir/Selenium/Webdriver. So, why not just reuse the test instead of maintaining the same test in 2 formats?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thankfully again, tsung comes with a recorder that allows us to generate our tests by running our user interface tests. This is an example of how to do that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id='get_your_popcorn'&gt;Get Your Popcorn&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;embed id='movie_player' height='385' type='application/x-shockwave-flash' src='http://www.youtube.com/v/AIfVUvsU4Fw?hd=1&amp;showinfo=0&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;et=OEgsToPDskJni4UfFH3f0WbK6L_15ohf&amp;amp;hl=en_US&amp;amp;fs=1' allowfullscreen='false' name='movie_player' style='' width='640' quality='high' /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#8217;s a &lt;a href='http://www.github.com/r351574nc3/ks-watir'&gt;github
project&lt;/a&gt; with example source code.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Testing out github gists</title>
   <link href="http://r351574nc3.github.io/none/2013/03/11/testing-out-github-gists"/>
   <updated>2013-03-11T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://r351574nc3.github.io/none/2013/03/11/testing-out-github-gists</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;script src='https://gist.github.com/r351574nc3/3054080.js?file=DemonstrationGradeEncryptionServiceImpl.java' /&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>TeamCity Beginner's Guide with Packt Publishing</title>
   <link href="http://r351574nc3.github.io/authoring/2013/03/11/teamcity-beginners-guide-with-packt-publishing"/>
   <updated>2013-03-11T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://r351574nc3.github.io/authoring/2013/03/11/teamcity-beginners-guide-with-packt-publishing</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id='whats_going_on'&gt;What&amp;#8217;s Going On?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was contracted by Packt Publishing to author a book about TeamCity Continuous Integration by JetBrains. I have authored a few publications before, but this is my first book. I&amp;#8217;m not sure how much time it will take out of my normal life to complete, but I am certainly up to the task.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#8217;s not much I can say about it until it is finished. I&amp;#8217;ll let everyone know about my experiences writing it and what chapter I&amp;#8217;m currently on. I can&amp;#8217;t say much about the book itself other than the progress I am making and what my personal feelings are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right now I am very excited about this book. It&amp;#8217;s going to be about 16 chapters long and I&amp;#8217;m currently wrapping up chapter 3. The pace is about a chapter every couple weeks, but I&amp;#8217;m behind. In fact, I went through a period early this year and late last year where I did absolutely nothing on it. I am trying to push forth a bit faster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id='about_the_book'&gt;About the Book&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This book is for people new to TeamCity and Continuous Integration. It provides several step-by-step instructions on how to use and configure TeamCity to work with your project. Project managers, configuration managers, and developers can use this tool to improve their Agile practices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It covers the basics for how to setup the software and get going with your first project. If you&amp;#8217;ve ever wondered how to get started with this software and needed an easy way to dive in right away, this book is exactly what you&amp;#8217;ve been waiting for. That&amp;#8217;s my sales pitch. Seriously though, I really cover just everything in the &amp;#8220;Beginner&amp;#8217;s&amp;#8221; realm.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Testing with JUnit Mini Book with Packt Publishing</title>
   <link href="http://r351574nc3.github.io/authoring/2013/03/11/junit-mini-book-with-packt-publishing"/>
   <updated>2013-03-11T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://r351574nc3.github.io/authoring/2013/03/11/junit-mini-book-with-packt-publishing</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h2 id='whats_going_on'&gt;What&amp;#8217;s Going On?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started another book in addition to the TeamCity book. This one is intended to go much faster. It&amp;#8217;s only 100 pages. At about 25 pages every couple weeks, this should be done in 2 months. My first chapter is due this week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id='about_the_book'&gt;About the Book&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For starters, it&amp;#8217;s just like the title implies. It&amp;#8217;s a mini book (about 100 pages) about JUnit. That said, JUnit implies unit testing with java and junit. Beyond that, this book is a cookbook or collection of howto&amp;#8217;s an recipies about writing really good JUnit tests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had a little time grasping just what context to use for java development. We&amp;#8217;re going to cover enterprise and web applications as well as some Android and mobile development. It&amp;#8217;s really exciting stuff.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most importantly, it&amp;#8217;s a very up-to-date book on modern unit testing and features of JUnit. It&amp;#8217;s also a good collection/reference for good unit test development and techniques. I cover several features of JUnit including exception handling and rules.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>내가 지저귀다</title>
   <link href="http://r351574nc3.github.io/2013/03/10/-"/>
   <updated>2013-03-10T00:00:00-07:00</updated>
   <id>http://r351574nc3.github.io/2013/03/10/-</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;내가 여기에서 지저귀다.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>